<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cathy Richards</title>
    <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cathy Richards</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 12:27:33 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://hi.cathyr.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/april-fools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/april-fools/</guid>
      <description>Whoever opened up the Jumanji game needs to put it the hell away. pic.twitter.com/vVqjLqJ9RK
&amp;mdash; K. Z. Howell (@KZ_Howell) March 27, 2020  I think we can all agree that it&amp;rsquo;s been a wild year. And while it&amp;rsquo;s been utterly exhausting, it&amp;rsquo;s been amazing in its own way.
With that said, some stories I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing here - others will be shared on my other blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tachyons for Style</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/tachyons-for-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/tachyons-for-style/</guid>
      <description>Tachyons is a design system that allows you to design gorgeous interfaces in the browser with little effort. Because Speed Building this static site generator theme was the first time I used an Atomic (or Functional) CSS system like Tachyons. It&amp;rsquo;s a design system that provides very small (which means fast) CSS modules that you can use in your HTML. So, rather than writing every line of CSS, you apply the style you need as you write your HTML with easy to understand shorthand class names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Scaffold</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</guid>
      <description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.” — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1
Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips. Most times, while fighting with floats and widths of content and sidebars or just basically trying to get something beside something else without using a stupid TABLE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Contact Form</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/built-in-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/blog/built-in-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website. Functional Form This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used. Please use your actual email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 14:47:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/about/</guid>
      <description>about me  Currently, I&#39;m working with the great team over at the The Engine Room as their Technical Project Manager. The Engine Room helps activists, organisations, and other social change agents make the most of data and technology to increase their impact. I&#39;m also co-founder at Pueblo CoLab - a collaborative aiming to help social innovators around the world do good work.
Surprisingly, I still spend a lot of time living out of my suitcase but feel most at home in Cape Town, Brooklyn or Costa Rica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title>
      <link>http://hi.cathyr.com/elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hi.cathyr.com/elements/</guid>
      <description>Font Sizes   A A A A A A A A   6rem
(96px) 5rem
(80px) 3rem
(48px) 2.25rem
(36px) 1.5rem
(24px) 1.25rem
(20px) 1rem
(16px) .875rem
(14px)     Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>